# Md Faisal Hossain



hello.faisalhossain@outlook.com



01814366774



linkedin.com/in/mdfaisalhossain1



https://web-faisal.github.io/profile/

# **Summary**

Hi, This is Faisal. I am a Web Developer & I am from Bangladesh. Experienced Data Entry Operator with a demonstrated history of working in the government administration industry. Skilled in Python (programming Language), JavaScript (programming Language), HTML( Hyper Text Markup Language), CSS (Cascading Style Sheets), SCSS(Senior Citizens Savings Scheme), Bootstrap(framework), React (framework), Node Js, git, bash Github, Unity (game engine), Filmora X, video editing & Microsoft office.

# **Experience**



## Web Developer

Fiverr

Dec 2020 - Present (11 months +)

### Youtube Content Creator

YouTube

Dec 2020 - Present (11 months +)

Develop original content through social listening and independent sources.

# Data Entry Operator

Income Tax Department, UK

Mar 2020 - Present (1 year 8 months +)

- Maintained databases, mailing lists, telephone networks, and other information to facilitate functioning of health education programs.
- Compiled [Timeframe] budget reports, financial spreadsheets and organizational charts to support business operations and improve office organization.

### **Education**



### Adarsha Pre-Cadet School

SSC

2020 - 2022

# **Skills**

Python (Programming Language) • JavaScript • GitHub • Video Editing • Bootstrap • React.js • Node js • Git BASH • HTML, css & SCSS • Bootstrap